<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Brewtopia</string>

    <string name="desc_img_splash_first">Background First Splash</string>
    <string name="headline_splash_first">FIND OUT</string>
    <string name="title_splash_first">ABOUT COFFEE BEANS</string>
    <string name="desc_splash_first">The ultimate refreshing drink to enjoy in every festival.</string>

    <string name="desc_img_splash_middle">Background Middle Splash</string>
    <string name="headline_splash_middle">CHOOSE</string>
    <string name="title_splash_middle">THE BEST COFFEE BEANS</string>
    <string name="desc_splash_middle">Never underestimate the power of a good cup of coffee.</string>

    <string name="desc_img_splash_last">Background Last Splash</string>
    <string name="headline_splash_last">TO MAKE</string>
    <string name="title_splash_last">SPECIAL COFFEE</string>
    <string name="desc_splash_last">I’m fueled by happy thoughts  and coffee.</string>

    <string name="menu_home_value">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_favorite_value">Favorite</string>
    <string name="menu_chat_value">Chat</string>
    <string name="menu_scan_value">Scan</string>

    <string name="desc_icon_menu">Icon Menu</string>
    <string name="desc_icon_search">Icon Search</string>

    <string name="desc_image_brewtopia_coffee">Brewtopia Coffee Image</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="recommendation">Recommendation</string>
    <string name="greeting">Hi Buddy!</string>
    <string name="get_it_now">Get It Now</string>

    <string name="sorry">Sorry, this page is currently under development.</string>
    <string name="page">Name of Page</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="account">Account</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="camera">Camera</string>
    <string name="identify">Identify</string>
    <string name="flash">Flash</string>
    <string name="choose_pic">Choose a picture</string>
    <string name="no_permission">No permission granted.</string>

    <string name="input_chat">Type a message ...</string>
    <string name="desc_send_icon">Send Icon</string>
    <string name="chatbot">ChatBot</string>

    <string name="coffee_scan">Coffee Scan</string>
    <string name="desc_border">Border for Image Upload</string>

    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="hint_pass">minimum 8 characters</string>
    <string name="hint_email">user@email.com</string>
    <string name="hint_name">write your name here…</string>
    <string name="signin">Sign In</string>
    <string name="signup">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password minimum 8 characters</string>
    <string name="invalid_email">Use valid email format</string>
    <string name="login_success">You are now logged in!</string>
    <string name="login_failed">Login failed!</string>

    <string name="failed_connection">Connection Failure</string>
    <string name="empty_name">Name cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="empty_email">Email cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="empty_pass">Password cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="logout_confirm">Do you really want to logout?</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="logged_out">Logged out</string>

    <string name="here_profile">Here are our profiles!</string>
    <string name="copyright">©Brewtopia_bangkit_2023</string>
    <string name="about_desc">Brewtopia is an application that we created to help entrepreneurs as well as coffee connoisseurs to know how to process the best quality coffee.</string>


    <string name="desc_camera">In BrewTopia, you can check your own coffee beans quality by taking picture via camera or choose your picture via gallery.</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="num_one">1</string>
    <string name="tips_first">Take a picture of the coffee beans from above.</string>
    <string name="num_two">2</string>
    <string name="tips_second">Use good lighting, try not to blur.</string>
    <string name="num_three">3</string>
    <string name="tips_third">Pay attention to the composition of your photos.</string>
    <string name="desc_upload_camera">Camera Icon to Upload</string>

    <string name="cofficles">Cofficles</string>
    <string name="features">Our Features</string>

    <string-array name="article_title">
        <item>Aroma is The Essence of Coffee</item>
        <item>Robusta Coffee Beyond Boldness</item>
        <item>Arabica Coffee The Elegance of Flavor</item>
        <item>Exploring the Types of Coffee Machines</item>
        <item>A Guide to the Perfect Brewing Coffee</item>
        <item>Good Coffee Composition: The Secret Behind a Delicious Cup</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="authors">
        <item>Mikael Rizki</item>
        <item>Imanuel Vicky</item>
        <item>Nadya Mumtazah</item>
        <item>Aldi Akbar</item>
        <item>Umar Hakim</item>
        <item>Christina Andrea</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="love">
        <item>176</item>
        <item>125</item>
        <item>214</item>
        <item>73</item>
        <item>34</item>
        <item>42</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="article_content">
        <item>Aroma plays a crucial role in the enchanting world of coffee.  From the moment the first droplets of steaming brew hit the air, the captivating fragrance takes hold, awakening our senses and drawing us closer to the rich flavors that await.\n\nThe enticing aroma of coffee is a result of the intricate chemistry that occurs during the roasting process. As the beans are exposed to heat, a symphony of volatile compounds is released, creating a bouquet of scents that range from earthy and nutty to floral and fruity.\n\nBut aroma is not just a pleasant sensory experience; it also contributes significantly to our perception of taste. The olfactory receptors in our noses work in tandem with our taste buds, allowing us to fully appreciate the intricate nuances of different coffee profiles.\n\nBeyond its impact on our senses, the aroma of coffee holds a nostalgic power. It has the ability to transport us back to cherished memories, evoking images of cozy mornings, lively conversations, or peaceful moments of solitude.\n\nFurthermore, coffee aficionados have mastered the art of discerning aromas, engaging in "cupping" sessions to evaluate and appreciate the unique scents of various coffee origins. They can detect subtle differences in fragrance, identifying notes of chocolate, caramel, citrus, or even floral undertones.\n\nWhether its the aroma of a freshly brewed cup or the scent lingering in a coffee shop, the allure of coffee fragrance is undeniable. It beckons us to indulge in its flavors, inviting us on a sensory journey with each sip.So, the next time you find yourself captivated by the aroma of coffee, take a moment to savor it fully. Allow the delicate notes to dance around your senses, transporting you to a realm where taste and aroma intertwine, creating a truly remarkable coffee experience.</item>
        <item>When it comes to coffee, one name that stands out is Robusta. Often overshadowed by its more famous counterpart, Arabica, Robusta has a distinctive character and a story of its own. While Arabica dominates the specialty coffee market, Robusta remains an important and widely consumed coffee variety.\n\nRobusta (Coffea canephora) is known for its robust nature, thriving in low-altitude regions and diverse climates. It is cultivated in several countries, including Vietnam, Brazil, and Indonesia, making it a significant player in the global coffee industry. Compared to Arabica, Robusta trees are more resistant to diseases and pests, making them easier to grow and maintain.\n\nOne notable characteristic of Robusta is its higher caffeine content. With nearly double the caffeine of Arabica, Robusta packs a powerful punch that appeals to those seeking a stronger and more energetic cup of joe. Its bold and full-bodied flavor profile often features earthy, woody, and even slightly bitter notes, which can be attributed to the higher levels of chlorogenic acids and caffeine.\n\nRobusta\s strong flavor profile makes it a popular choice for espresso blends, where its intense and lingering aftertaste complements the milk and other ingredients. Additionally, it is frequently used in instant coffee production due to its affordability and ability to retain flavors during the manufacturing process.\n\nWhile Robusta may have been dismissed by some coffee enthusiasts in the past, its reputation is gradually changing. Specialty coffee producers are now exploring the potential of Robusta, showcasing its unique qualities and creating specialty-grade Robusta coffees. These specialty Robusta offerings highlight the distinct flavors and aromas that can be found within this variety, challenging the notion that Arabica is the only coffee worthy of attention.\n\nFurthermore, Robusta plays a crucial role in sustainability and economic development for coffee-growing regions. Its higher productivity and resilience make it a vital source of income for farmers in areas where Arabica struggles to thrive. By embracing and supporting Robusta cultivation, the coffee industry can contribute to the livelihoods of communities and promote sustainability in the coffee supply chain.\n\nIn conclusion, Robusta coffee is much more than its bold reputation suggests. It possesses unique characteristics, a higher caffeine content, and a flavor profile that is appreciated by many. As the coffee industry evolves and consumers become more adventurous in their coffee choices, Robustas place in the spotlight is gradually being recognized. So, the next time you crave a cup of coffee that packs a punch, dont overlook Robusta—it might just surprise you with its boldness and complexity.</item>
        <item>When it comes to specialty coffee, one name that consistently comes up is Arabica. Renowned for its exquisite flavors and complex profiles, Arabica coffee has captured the hearts of coffee enthusiasts around the world. Let\s delve into the captivating world of Arabica and explore what makes it so exceptional.\n\nArabica (Coffea arabica) is considered the superior coffee species, known for its delicate nuances and refined taste. Grown in high-altitude regions with ideal climates and fertile soil, Arabica beans develop slowly, allowing the flavors to mature and deepen. This slow growth process contributes to the complexity and sophistication that characterizes Arabica coffee.\n\nOne of the defining features of Arabica is its wide range of flavors. From fruity and floral to nutty and chocolatey, Arabica exhibits a diverse flavor spectrum that tantalizes the taste buds. These flavors arise from the combination of genetic traits, terroir (environmental factors such as soil and climate), and meticulous processing methods employed by coffee producers.\n\nThe acidity level in Arabica coffee is another notable aspect that sets it apart. Arabica beans typically possess a balanced and nuanced acidity, often described as bright or lively. This acidity contributes to the overall complexity of the coffee, adding a refreshing and vibrant dimension to the flavor profile.\n\nMoreover, Arabica is known for its smooth and silky mouthfeel. When brewed properly, it produces a velvety texture that glides across the palate, enhancing the overall drinking experience. This luxurious mouthfeel is a result of the optimal balance between sugars, oils, and acids found within the beans.\n\nIn addition to its outstanding taste, Arabica is often celebrated for its lower caffeine content compared to Robusta. While the exact caffeine levels vary depending on various factors, Arabica generally contains less caffeine, making it a preferred choice for those seeking a milder and more nuanced coffee experience.</item>
        <item>Coffee has become an integral part of our daily lives, and having a reliable coffee machine at home or in the office can elevate our coffee experience. With various types of coffee machines available, let\s take a closer look at some popular options and discover their unique features.\n\nDrip Coffee Maker:\nThe drip coffee maker is a classic and widely used machine. It operates by pouring water over coffee grounds held in a filter, allowing the brewed coffee to drip into a carafe below. Drip coffee makers are known for their simplicity, convenience, and ability to brew multiple cups of coffee at once. They are an excellent choice for those seeking a hassle-free brewing method.\n\nEspresso Machine:\nEspresso machines are designed to brew concentrated and flavorful shots of espresso. They work by forcing hot water through finely ground coffee under high pressure, resulting in a rich and intense beverage. Espresso machines offer the versatility to create various espresso-based drinks like cappuccinos, lattes, and macchiatos. They are favored by coffee enthusiasts who appreciate the art of espresso preparation.\n\nFrench Press:\nThe French press, also known as a press pot or plunger pot, is a manual coffee brewing device. It consists of a cylindrical carafe and a plunger with a metal filter. To brew coffee with a French press, you add coarsely ground coffee and hot water, let it steep for a few minutes, and then press the plunger to separate the coffee grounds from the liquid. French press coffee is praised for its full-bodied flavor and robustness.\n\nSingle-Serve Coffee Maker:\nSingle-serve coffee makers, such as pod or capsule machines, have gained popularity for their convenience and efficiency. These machines use pre-packaged coffee pods or capsules, which contain the right amount of coffee for a single serving. With a simple push of a button, you can enjoy a freshly brewed cup of coffee without the need for grinding or measuring. Single-serve coffee makers offer a wide range of coffee flavors and styles to choose from.\n\nPour-Over Coffee Maker:\nPour-over coffee makers provide a more hands-on and artisanal coffee brewing experience. They typically consist of a carafe or dripper with a filter. The process involves pouring hot water over coffee grounds in a slow and controlled manner, allowing the flavors to extract gradually. Pour-over brewing allows for precise control over factors like water temperature and flow rate, resulting in a customized and nuanced cup of coffee.\n\nThese are just a few examples of the many types of coffee machines available in the market. Each machine offers a unique approach to brewing coffee, allowing you to explore different flavors, strengths, and brewing methods. Ultimately, the choice of coffee machine depends on your preferences, lifestyle, and desired level of involvement in the brewing process.\n\nSo, whether you opt for a classic drip coffee maker, an espresso machine for your daily dose of caffeine, or a French press for a rich and immersive experience, there is a coffee machine out there to suit your needs and help you enjoy a delightful cup of coffee whenever you desire.</item>
        <item>Brewing coffee is not just a routine, it\s an art that allows us to savor the rich flavors and aromas locked within those humble coffee beans. Whether you\re a coffee aficionado or a beginner looking to enhance your brewing skills, here\s a step-by-step guide to help you achieve the perfect cup of coffee.\n\nStart with Freshly Roasted Beans:\nThe foundation of a great cup of coffee lies in the beans. Choose high-quality, freshly roasted coffee beans for optimal flavor. Look for beans with a roast date to ensure freshness.\n\nGrind the Beans:\nFor the best flavor, grind your coffee beans just before brewing. The grind size will vary depending on the brewing method you choose. Finer grinds are typically used for espresso, while coarser grinds work well for French press or pour-over methods.\n\nMeasure the Coffee and Water:\nUse the right coffee-to-water ratio for a well-balanced cup. A general guideline is to use one to two tablespoons of coffee for every six ounces of water. Adjust the ratio based on your taste preferences.\n\nChoose the Brewing Method:\nThere are various brewing methods available, each offering a unique coffee experience. Some popular options include drip brewing, espresso machines, French press, pour-over, and AeroPress. Select a method that suits your preferences and equipment availability.\n\nPreheat and Prepare:\nPreheat your brewing equipment to ensure optimal extraction. For example, preheat your French press by adding hot water and letting it sit for a few minutes before discarding the water. This helps maintain the desired brewing temperature.\n\nBrew Time and Temperature:\nPay attention to the brewing time and temperature, as they significantly impact the final taste. Different brewing methods require specific water temperatures and extraction times. Generally, aim for water temperatures between 195°F to 205°F (90°C to 96°C) and adjust accordingly.\n\nBrew with Care:\nFollow the specific instructions for your chosen brewing method. Whether its pouring water in a circular motion over coffee grounds, adjusting pressure and extraction time for espresso, or allowing the coffee to steep in a French press, give each step the attention it deserves.\n\nTaste and Adjust:\nOnce your coffee is brewed, its time to taste and fine-tune. Take a moment to savor the flavors and aromas. If needed, adjust the coffee-to-water ratio, grind size, or brewing time to achieve your desired taste profile.\n\nServe and Enjoy:\nPour your freshly brewed coffee into your favorite mug or cup. Consider adding a splash of milk or a dash of sweetener, depending on your preferences. Take a moment to appreciate the aroma, the richness, and the warmth as you indulge in your perfectly brewed cup of coffee.\n\nRemember, brewing coffee is a journey of exploration and experimentation. Dont be afraid to try different beans, brewing methods, or techniques to find your perfect cup. With practice, patience, and attention to detail, youll master the art of brewing coffee and create a truly delightful coffee experience every time.</item>
        <item>Coffee is a beverage that holds its own uniqueness, and one crucial factor in creating a delightful flavor is a good coffee composition. During the coffee-making process, there are several key components that contribute to the overall taste and quality of the brew.\n\nFirst and foremost, the quality of the coffee beans plays a vital role. Opt for freshly roasted beans that are sourced from reputable suppliers. Arabica and Robusta are two popular varieties known for their distinct flavors. Experiment with different origins and blends to find the one that suits your taste preferences.\n\nNext, the grind size is crucial in determining the extraction level and flavor intensity. Coarser grinds are ideal for methods like French press or cold brew, while finer grinds are suitable for espresso or pour-over brewing. Consistency in grind size ensures even extraction and a balanced flavor profile.\n\nWater quality is often overlooked but can significantly affect the taste of your coffee. Ideally, use filtered or bottled water to avoid any unwanted flavors or impurities. The water temperature should be between 195°F to 205°F (90°C to 96°C) for optimal extraction.\n\nLastly, the coffee-to-water ratio is essential in achieving the right balance. As a general guideline, a ratio of 1:16 (1 part coffee to 16 parts water) is commonly used. However, feel free to adjust it according to your personal preference for a stronger or milder cup of coffee.\n\nRemember, the key to a good coffee composition lies in experimentation and finding the perfect balance that suits your taste buds. With the right combination of high-quality beans, proper grind size, good water quality, and the ideal coffee-to-water ratio, youll be able to brew a cup of coffee that is both flavorful and satisfying. So, grab your favorite beans, follow these guidelines, and embark on a delightful coffee journey. Cheers!</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="article_banner">
        <item>@drawable/banner_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/banner_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/banner_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/banner_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/banner_5</item>
        <item>@drawable/banner_6</item>
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="article_cover">
        <item>@drawable/cover_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/cover_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/cover_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/cover_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/cover_5</item>
        <item>@drawable/cover_6</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string name="linkedin">Linkedin</string>
    <string name="desc_image_scan">Illustration For Scan</string>
    <string name="desc_image_chat">Illustration For Chat</string>
    <string name="scan">Scan</string>
    <string name="favorite">Favorite</string>

    <!--developers-->
    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>Aldi Akbar Alimi</item>
        <item>Christina Andrea Putri</item>
        <item>Mikael Rizki Pandu Ekanto</item>
        <item>Imanuel Vicky Sanjaya</item>
        <item>Umar Hakim</item>
        <item>Nadya Mumtazah</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--linkedin-->
    <string-array name="linkedin">
        <item>https://www.linkedin.com/in/aldiakbaralimi/</item>
        <item>https://www.linkedin.com/in/christinandrea/</item>
        <item>https://www.linkedin.com/in/mikaelrizki</item>
        <item>https://www.linkedin.com/in/imanuel-vicky-s</item>
        <item>https://www.linkedin.com/in/umar-hakim-65a32b1b7/</item>
        <item>https://www.linkedin.com/in/nadya-mumtazah-662519206/</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--developer profile-->
    <integer-array name="profile_dev">
        <item>@drawable/img_profil_aldi</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_profil_tina</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_profil_kiki</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_profil_nuel</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_profil_umar</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_profil_nadya</item>
    </integer-array>
</resources>